好的 你太厉害了
OK, you're great
绳索绑好了吗? 是的 快爬吧 慢郎中
You've got the line? Yeah, come up slow folk
你没事吧?
You're OK?
你知道方圆五十英里内半个人影也没 你在对谁鬼叫啊?
You know in 50 miles there isn't anybody. Who are you screaming for?
你啊快点!
You. Come on.
拉我上去
Pull me up.
瑞奇
Rich
拉我上去啦
Just pull me up.
好了 别耍贱了 瑞奇 我需要有人拉我一下
Alright, don't be a dick, Richie I need a pull.
瑞奇
Rich
(西维吉尼亚州)
(山地人不朽传奇)
(近亲交配导致脸部畸形)
(遗传突变)
《致命弯道》
(近亲交配所产生的精神异常)
(失踪悬赏)
(筏夫失踪)
(暴动爆发)
(失踪人口)
(登山客失踪)
(迷路女孩失踪)
(失踪女孩)
(本地女孩失踪)
(西维吉尼亚州 绿蔷薇偏僻乡下)
瑞奇史托佛和艾蒂丝史密斯 自上周一起就失踪了
Richard Stover and Edith Smith have been missing since last Monday.
截至周末为止尚未返回...
Have been failing to return from a weekend at rock...
你好
How are you doing?
你知道前面怎么了吗?
You've got any idea what's going on up here?
前方约五英里处交通堵塞 化学物流的满地都是
Traffic jacked about 5 mile up Still chemicals to shit all over the road.
知道多久能清除完毕吗?
Any idea how long it would take to clean up?
几个小时吧
Couple of hours.
几个小时?
Couple of hours
你赶时间?
You're in a hurry.
对 我必须赶到罗里 且我...
Yeah I need to take to Roli and I...
那你只能回你车上 重新另抄一条捷径看看啰
What you should do is get back in your car pick your short cut one more time.
谢谢
Thank you
嘿 桃乐丝我是克里斯弗林
Hey Doris, this is Chris Flinn
我下午三点要与凯勒先生面试
I have at3 PM an interview with Mr. Keller.
大概会迟到半个钟头 不知道你能不能...
I'm arriving about 30 minutes later, so I wonder if you could...
喂?
Hello?
怎么会这样?
How can it make this?
(距加油站一英里远)
抱歉 先生 你们有公共电话吗?
Excuse me, sir Do you have a pay phone?
这支坏掉了 还有别支电话可以借我打吗?
This one's not working. Do you have another phone I can use?
打长途的?
Long distance?
从这里打有哪里不是长途?
What isn't long distance from here, alright?
你在对我吼吗 孩子?
You got wild at me, son?
不是的 先生 我只是... 我有点迟了 我真的需要打通电话
No, sir, I'm just... I'm running behind, I really need to make a call.
那是我仅有的电话了
Well that is my only phone.
好吧
Right
对 公路上塞车 你知道别条路可以通出去吗?
Yeah, highway road is jammed up. Do you know of another road heading us out?
不知道
No
这条山路怎么会像这样涂上颜色?
Why is this certain mountain road dyed like this?
它们是路?
They're road?
但他们还没重印地图呢
But they ain't go around the paper yet.
看来走这条路约有15、20英里路程 对吗?
It looks like it runs in the highway about 15, 20 miles, is that right?
你说是就是
You say so.
好极了
Good work
非常感谢 保重了 好吗?
Thank you very much Take care, ok?
你才需要好好保重
You are the one gonna need take care.
(熊山路)
你还好吧?
You're alright?
真的很抱歉 我刚好...
I'm so sorry, I just...
我刚回过头 没注意到...
I just come from the back, I didn't even see...
分神了 天哪 你可能撞死呢
I got distracted Oh God, you could die.
你们全都没事吧? 是的 你想坐下来吗?
You guys are all OK? Yeah, You wanna sit down?
你可能会有脑震荡
You might be in a state of shock
你到底在干嘛? 开车开的那么快 好了 好了
What the hell are you doing? You're driving so god damn fast Alright, alright
你的车怎会停在路中间? 因为轮胎破了啊混蛋
How was your truck parked in the middle of the road? Because you broke our tyre, you asshole.
听着 我会赔偿我撞坏的一切损失
Look, I will pay for everything I've damaged.
听着 妈的 没错 你要赔偿 那是我妈的车子呢
Look, damn, you're right, you're gonna pay, that's my Mom's car.
好了 大伙 这人说会赔的...
Alright, friends, the man said he'd pay for it...
看来你毁了我的自行车
Looks like you killed my bike here.
对不起
I'm sorry
你的车胎怎会破了呢?
How did you ruin your tyres?
有人在路中央放置了铁丝网
Someone left some barb wires in the middle of the road.
不敢相信竟然有人将它掉在这里 没有人掉了什么
I can't believe someone just dropped it there. Nobody dropped anything.
我刚发现铁丝网一端固定在树后面 是有人故意的
I just found found it tied to the tree back there. Somebody did this.
他们的待客之道太差了 该死的混蛋!
Their hospitality is worse Redneck assholes!
听着 我要设法弄支电话 我想后面几英里处有座加油站
Look, I'm going to try to find a phone. I think there's a gas station a couple of miles back.
我跟你去
I'm gonna come with you.
没有电话 我刚刚去过了
There is no phone. I was just there.
我们何不等别人经过呢? 像这儿的赛车手一样吗?
Why don't we wait for someone else to come along? Well, like speedracer here?
听着 我哪里也不去 好的
Look, I'm not going anywhere. Ok?
你们去吧 我不知道 我们要留在这里 法兰西...
You guys go I dont' know, we're gonna stay here, Francine
...好好享受一番 对 那又怎样?
and get high Yeah, so what?
嘿 你叫什么名字?
Hey, what's your name?
克里斯弗林
Chris Flinn
你受伤了 克里斯弗林?
You hurt, Chris Flinn?
不 我没事
I'm fine.
很好
Good
因为你是骡子
cause you're the mule.
不 那个我来背就行 你决定整部车或什么的就好
Oh no I can carry that. You decide the whole car or something.
我们待在这里 也许又会被撞... 你们确定都没事吗?
We'll just stay here, maybe get hit again... You guys sure you're cool?
是的 我们好的很 谢谢
Yeah, we're just fine. Thank you.
晚点见了 慢慢抽吧 小捣蛋
Later on. Smoke it up there, skippie?
是的 祝你们愉快
Yeah, have fun.
你想被它害死吗?
You want it to kick your ass.
老天 刚才发生的事我还心有余悸呢
God I can't let out of my head what was just happending.
你确定你真的没事吗? 是的 我没事
You're sure you're just alright? Yeah, I'm fine
你们来这里做什么?
What are you guys doing out here?
好的 我不知道 事实上我们迷路了
OK, I don't know, actually we're lost
你知道很多人说我们一直 重覆经历往后的时光
You know a lot of people say we've been to some ??? experiences, the following moments.
有点像是慢动作前后移动
Kind of feel like moving and turning in slow motion
你有同感吗? 没有
Do you feel like that? No
我该告诉你我的声音在正常速度下 真的很小声低沉
I should tell you that my voice is really low and down in normal speed.
怪了
Weird
你在哪拿到的?
Where did you get this?
天啊我爸太好了
God my Dad's very nice.
我抽不完这根
I couldn't finish this.
我们可以想想怎么抽吗?
Can we figure how to stone this?
你确定知道我们往哪走吗? 是的 加油站有地图
Are you sure you know where we're going? Yeah, there was a map at gas station.
我已经筋疲力尽快饿死了 还被蚂蚁咬我
I'm so tired already and starving and being eaten by ants.
我背上有蚂蚁吗? 没有 什么也没有
Are there any on my back? No, nothing there
我叫它松鼠
I call it squirrel.
你说你饿了吗 卡莉? 我认为不是松鼠
Are you saying you are hungry, Carly? I don't think it's a squirrel.
是标本
It's a make.
真的? 你怎么知道? 可能是被他辗过去的
Really? How do you know? He probably ran over it.
在医学院里 他们让你用动物作实验
In medical school they make you work on animal
因为我怕用活的东西
cause I was afraid to get the real thing.
是标本
It's a make.
我得在七点前赶到罗里
I need to be in Roli by 7.
那最好动作快点了
Better get move on then
你知道我们选择定居纽约
You know we choose to take it in New York.
不 若非被困 你我应该看看
No, you and I should look except we're stuck.
是的
Yeah
洁西意思是说整个大自然真烂
Jess mean, whole nature sucks.
下回你被甩了时 我会对你这么说的
Well, the next time you get dumped, I'm take it to you.
裤子脱掉
Drop your pants.
什么?
What?
何时会有人一直出现呢 艾凡? 我们要干嘛?
When do people always show, Evan? What are we doing?
当作是机率理论的实验吧
Consider it an experiment of probability theory.
真的
Really
我爱你 我知道
I love you. I know.
那裤子脱了吧 小子 别婆婆妈妈的 好的
Then get your trousers off, boy. Don't be a sissy Alright
宝贝 我一直在考虑这整件事 整个婚事以及...
Baby, I've been thinking about this whole, this whole wedding thing and.
我觉得我们应该下周把这事做个解决
I think we should take this done next week
我在说的是在玛格丽特度个漫长周末 我们两人独自在海边欣赏日落
I'm talking about a long weekend at Margarita's, two of us at beach alone, sunset.
我在说的是... 微不足道的事 你懂我的意思吧?
And I'm talking about... Just the low thing. You know what I mean?
是的 你等一下
Yeah, you wait a second
你想知道我的想法吗?
You wanna know what I think.
是的 请说
Yes, please
我觉得如果你还想钻进我的裤子里 是的 那是肯定的
I think if you ever want to get in my pants again. Yes, that's affirm
这是你最后一次讲"淫"话了 好吗?
This is the last time you use the "E" word. OK?
我明白 恶心的字
I see, disgusting word.
嘿 各位 等等
Hey, guys, hold on.
嘿 上面有人吗?
Hey, is anyone up there?
喂?
Hello?
附近一定有人 上面有人吗?
There must be people nearby. Anyone up there?
有人始作俑者
Somebody had it just started.
我们继续走吧
Let's keep moving.
喂?
Hello.
看看这个 挂了
Look at this. It's fucked.
没事
Nothing.
你有找到吃的吗? 他们拔走我的电瓶
Hey, did you find anything to eat? They took all my power box.
没有! 没有 对不起
No! No, sorry.
该死
Damn it
不见了 卡莉拿走我们所有的防晒用品
It's gone. Carly took all our freaking sunscreen.
有看见好听的CD吗?
See any of good cd's?
绝对没有
Definitely not.
你知道吗? 我觉得这家伙一定是某种医生
You know I think this guy must be some kind of doctor.
等他回来 叫他开些处方笺
We'll get him to write some prescriptions when he gets back.
这里也没也很多烟 几乎没有
Here's not many smoke either. Almost out.
艾凡?
Evan?
艾凡? 你在哪里?
Evan? Where are you?
嘿 宝贝 你在干嘛?
Hey baby, what are you doing?
我在自我作乐呢
I'm amusing myself.
你赶去那边有重要事吗 查理? 没有 我已经错过了
You're getting anything there, Charlie No nothing. I've already missed the thing
你为何不用飞的?
Why didn't you just fly?
我的钱都放在那辆车子上
Put all my money back in that car there.
好的 别管细节了
OK, forget aloping
但我们应该讨论一下我们婚礼的乐队
But there's an idea we should discuss about the band for our wedding.
我们应该雇法兰克辛纳屈那一型的 来当乐队主唱
We should hire a Frank Sinatra type lead singer for the band
不要请詹姆斯布朗那型的做主唱
Opposed to a James Brown type lead singer.
因为真的 坦白说 只有一个詹姆斯布朗
Because really, let's be honest, there's only one James Brown
假的詹姆斯布朗真的教人受不了
Foul James Brown is really quite intoleralbe
艾凡? 你在哪里?
Evan? Where are you?
你在尿尿还是干嘛?
You pissing or something?
艾凡?
Evan?
你要是毛毛躁躁弄脏了屁股 连我奶奶也会讨厌你的
You're fussy begriming the hips And my Grandma would be, yes revolted, but also.
她是满古怪的会让你觉得不安
Strangely fascinated in a completely disturbing way. And...
宝贝
Babe
卡莉 我开玩笑的! 卡莉?
Carly, I was kidding, Carly.
艾凡?
Evan?
甜心?
Sweetheart?
嘿 大伙 等等
Hey guys, hold up.
大伙 等一下好吗?
Guys, hold up for a second, alright?
宝贝 说真的 这不好玩
Baby, seriously this isn't funny
天啊宝贝
Gee, God, baby
住手
Stop
真是抱歉 我很可能杀了你 我是极端危险的
I'm so sorry. I could've killed you, woman, I'm extremely dangerous.
你想知道我为什么这么爱你吗?
You wanna know why I love you so much?
因为你可以陪我玩 所以你才爱我
Because you're someone to play with. That's why you love me
那真的吓我一跳 宝贝 对不起
That really scared me baby. Sorry.
真的吓我一跳 别再那样子行吗?
That really scared me, would you not do that?
喂?
Hello
显然作过声明了 是吧?
There is a statement obviously, huh?
嘿 宝贝 瞧瞧这个
Hey, baby, look at this.
卡莉 我觉得现在这里刚好...
Hey Carly, I think it's here a good time to...
不
Don't
好了 那不好玩 看看谁吓谁
Ok, that is not funny. Look who scared now.
抱歉 管你的
Sorry. Whatever.
只管送我到汽车旅馆房间里
Just get me to a motel room,
让我洗个舒服的热水澡 准备教我高潮迭起
run me a very hot bath and be prepared to provide mewith a lot of orgasms.
我想他们需要独处一下
I think they need to be alone.
你还能怎么想? 他们刚订婚 他们很幸福
What do you expect? They just got engaged. They're happy.
所以我想他们没事了 是的
So I think they're fine. Yeah
没问题吧? 没问题
Got it? ???, got it.
你真笨
You're stupid
也许我们不该丢下法兰西和艾凡不管 别担心 他们会没事的
Maybe we shouldn't have left Francine and Evan. Don't worry, they're fine
你们还好吧? 好极了
You guys are OK? Super.
等等 各位 这条路不是在这上面...
Woah wait guys, this road isn't on here..
那是因为你又没有乡下人的地图
That's because you don't have the redneck world atlas.
我想我们刚得救了呢 各位 我能起来吗?
I think we've just been saved, kids. Can I get up?
弄快点
Make this quick.
说真的 也许我们该继续行进
Actually, maybe we should keep walking.
为什么 等下一栋可能有 白色栅栏的房子吗?
For what, the next house that might have a white picket fence.
或也许再下一栋房子
Or maybe for the next house.
嘿! 怎么?
Hey What?
喂?
Hello.
好了 这样不对
Alright, this isn't right.
喂?
Hello.
喂? 有人在家吗?
Hello. Anybody home?
宝贝 你可不可以...?
Woah, baby, would you, could you?
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
我看看有没有电话 愿意的话你们可以在外头等着
I'm gonna see if they had a phone. Mabye you guys can wait out here if you want.
你不能那样子闯入别人家里
You can't just barge in someone's house like that.
对 因为你知道我在想什么 在西维吉尼亚州 非法侵入可不是件好事
Yeah, because you know I'm thinking, West Virginia, trespassing, not a good combination.
听着 我要尿尿
Look, I need to pee.
我得提醒你一部叫做"激流四勇士"的电影
Well, I need to remind you of a little movie called "Deliverance"
各位 我们两辆车都撞烂了 我们真的需要打电话
Guys, we have two wreck cars, and we really need a phone.
喂?
Hello
卡莉
Carly
喂?
Hello
搞什么...?!
What the fuck
我们办好要做的事 赶紧离开这里
Let's just do what we gotta do and get out of here
好了 我看这里是没有电话了
OK, I have not sensed a phone here
喂?
Hello
好的 谁住在这里? 不知道 但你能帮我找一下厕所在哪吗?
OK, who lives here? I don't know, but can you help me find the bathroom?
宝贝 我想这就是厕所
Baby, I think this is the bathroom.
干
Fuck
真的 各位 我想我们该离开
Seriously, guys, I think we should go.
好的 帮我找一下厕所再走
OK, just help me find the bathroom, and then we go
宝贝 这地方就像某种庭院 事实上我读过一份周报...
Baby this place is just like some kind of court. Actually I read a Newsweek...
经济萧条地区就像孕育各种邪教的源地
economically depressed places are like breeding grounds for all kinds of apocalyptic visionaries.
找了间旧寺庙... 西莎家族 记得他们吗?
Ordered this old temple ??? The Sisha Family. Remember them?
嘿 智者
Hey, brainiac.
好了 也许是那扇门
Alright, maybe that door.
克里斯 你没事吧? 没事 只是船桨 没事的
Chris, you're OK? Yeah, just a paddle, it's alright
天哪 看看这地方 没错 像地狱草原
God, look at this place. Yeah, like the grass from hell.
老天
Jesus
克里斯
Chris
我们该走了
We should leave
对 这里没错 好的 快点
Yeah, this is it. Ok, be quick
两分钟好吗? 我在这里等你
Two minutes, alright? I'll be here
各位 来看看这个
Guys, guys, check this out.
天啊史考特 史考特
Oh God, Scott, Scott
史考特 我们必须马上离开
Scott, we have to go now.
洁西 洁西
Jess, Jessie
各位 听好了 我们必须回头找你的朋友 电话怎么办? 没有电话
Hey, guys, listen. We need to get back to your friends. What about the phone? There is no phone
该死
Shit
有后门 走后门 快点 走! 走! 走!
There is a backdoor. Let's go backdoor, come on. Go, go go
快 快!
Hurry, hurry
妈的! 不
Shit! No.
史考特! 史特特!
Scott, Scott
打不开了 来吧
It's not gonna bolt, come on.
来吧
Come
快走!
Go!
走! 走! 走! 不 你必须快逃
Go, go, go. No, you have to run
他们要去哪里? 不知道
Where are they going. I don't know.
天啊刚刚是真的发生了?
Jesus, that really just happened?
你想法兰西没事吧?
Do you think Francine is OK?
我起不来
I can't get it.
快点 起来
Come on, get up.
你没看见他们对法兰西做了什么 你没看见我们所看见的
You didn't see what they did to Francine You didn't see what we saw.
卡莉 甜心 看着我 我们会逃出去的 我发誓
Carly, sweetie. Look at me. We're gonna get out of here, I swear you, we are
好的 我们会找到路到达镇上 我们会回家
OK. We're gonna find a road and we're gonna get to a town. We're going home.
我们会结婚 好吗?
We're gonna get married. Alright?
从此不再到森林里来
And we're never going into the woods again.
我们快走 快点 走这边
We get to go. Come on, this way.
这怎么了?
What is this?
天哪
Jesus
这些废铁我们怎么逃走? 哦 我的天啊这些人全都...
How do we get away with this? Oh my God, all these people
快逃吧 他们还在附近
Take run, they're still around us
找找钥匙 我们还是能逃出去的
Look for keys. We still get to run
趴下 趴下
Get down, get down.
我们怎么办?
What do we do?
他的卡车还在发动 所以呢? 我们要去抢
He left the truck on. So? We're gonna take it.
我们要怎么办的到?
How are we supposed to do that?
我们其中一个引诱他们到别处 然后剩下的人跑到卡车那里
One of us leads them in the wrong direction. And the rest come to the truck.
经典 谁去?
It's a classical note. Who goes?
我
Me.
我在这里!
I'm here!
听着 我会上卡车的 稍后和你会合
Listen, I'm gonna get the truck on I'll meet you back.
烂人 全你他妈的烂人 混蛋
Fuckers, all you mother fuckers, asshole
他没事
He's OK.
快点
Come on.
走! 走!
Go go.
我们得离开 快点 我不行
We gotta go, come on I can't
我们得去找史考特 我们必须去找史考特
We gotta find Scott, we have to find Scott
他在哪里?
Where is he?
他在那里
There is he.
史考特 我们在这里!
Scott, we're here!
快点 加油!
Hurry, go!
快点 史考特
Come on Scott.
你在干嘛? 史考特 怎么了?
What are you doing? Scott, what's wrong?
史考特 不
Scott, no
放开我 放开我
Let go of me Let me go.
史考特
Scott
开车 开车!
Drive, drive!
天啊!
Oh God
天啊怎么回事?
Oh God, what's happening?
拜讬 我们开回去好吗?
Yes please, can we go back?
卡莉 我们必须继续前进 好吗?
Carly, we have to keep going. Ok?
你确定地图上是写这条路吗? 一定能通到某个地方
You're sure this is the road from that map? It's gotta go somewhere.
最好能带我们离开这儿
It's better get us out of here.
可恶
Shit
快点
Come on.
倒车
Back it up.
快点 没办法往前了
Come on. We can't go any further.
我们必须查清楚我们的位置 最高山脊在那边 快点
We gotta find out where we are. The highest ridge is up there. Come on.
洁西 我只想待在原地不动
Jess, I just like staying
快点 走吧 卡莉 不
Come on, go Carly No
卡莉 看着我 好吗? 史考特为了保护我们而死
Carly, look at me, OK? Scott died protecting us.
我们必须活命 否则他这么做 就没有价值了 懂吗?
We need to keep ourselves alive, whatver it's for nothing. OK?
我们要同舟共济 快点
We are all in this together. Come on
我要他回来
I want him back.
看着我 好吗? 看着我
Look at me, OK? Look
我们会活下去 我们会逃出去的
We're gonna stay alive, we're gonna get out of this.
我们会逃出这片森林
We're gonna get of these woods,
找到警察 我们会确认那些混帐会因此受到惩罚的
we're gonna find policemen we're gonna make sure those motherfuckers are punished for this. OK?
卡莉
Carly
快点 卡莉 你行的
Come on Carl.y You can do it.
天色越来越暗了 所以快一点
It's gonna get dark. So come on
我们快点找出条路 我知道
Let's find the road quick. I know
才走了一英里 还好远呢
Just a mile, but farther
克里斯
Chris
真是噩梦
It's a bad dream.
怎么了? 我得休息一下
What's up? I gotta rest.
嘿 各位 你们看
Hey, guys. Look.
哦 我的天啊
Oh my God
是了望塔台
It's a watch tower.
喂 上面有人吗?
Hello, anyone up there?
我想上面没人 没关系 或许有电话或无线电呢
I don't think anyone's up there. Doesn't matter, Maybe there's a phone or radio.
也许我们能看到路面 你没事吧?
Maybe we'll see the road. You're OK?
快点
Come on.
各位 我看不到路及城镇 别站靠窗附近 会被他们看到
Guys, I don't see any road. The towns are out there Let's not stand by the window, they will see us.
过来 我们会死的
Come here We're gonna die
卡莉 我要你清醒一下看看周围 拜讬
Carly, I need you to come out and look around, please.
嘿 克里斯
Hey, Chris
洁西 谢谢
Jess. Thanks.
天啊是无线电
Oh my God, it's a radio.
这东西还相当耐用
Thing works pretty stark
你知道怎么操作吗? 让我试试
Do you know how to use this? Let me try
我想还能用 别乱动 继续试试所有频道
I think it still works. Don't move anything, just keep on all the frequencies they had on.
有人听见吗? 我们有紧急事故 有人听见吗?
Can anybody hear me? We have an emergency. Can anybody hear me?
听着 我们遇上重大紧急事故 拜讬 有人听见吗?
Look, we have a huge emergency, please, is there anybody hear me.
有人受伤了 我们需要救助
Someone is injured. We need a help.
拜讬 外面有人听见我吗? 喂?
Please, is there anybody out that can hear me? Hello
不
No
趴下 灯光盖住
Get down Cover the light.
我们他们过去了
I think they're passing us.
这是报案中心 收的到吗? 你的位置在哪?
This is ???. Can you copy? Where is your position?
听到了吗? 你们位置在哪里?
Do you copy? Where's your position?
我不清楚我的位置 帮帮我们就是
I don't know my position. Just help us.
没听到 请重覆 你的位置在哪 他们来了
I didn't copy that, repeat, what is your position. They're coming
收到 我们不知道我们的位置 我们在一座了望塔 一定在北边
Copy, we don't know our position, we're in a watchtower. We must be in north of ???
有人想杀我们 拜讬 他们杀害了我们的朋友 快救救我们
Someone's trying to kill us.Please. They've murdered our friends. Help us right now
留在原地 收到了吗?
Stay there, do you copy?
是的 收到 请派警察过来 这是紧急事故
Yes, I copy Just bring the police, this is an emergency.
帮我搬这个 快
Help me move this, come.
有人中弹了 我们朋友被杀了 拜讬救救我们
Someone's been shot, Out friends have been killed. Help us out, please
干
Fuck
他们在干嘛?
What are they doing?
不清楚
I don't know
我想他们下去了
I think they're going down.
洁西
Jess
喂 喂 有人在吗? 听得见我们吗? 喂?
Hello, hello, is there anybody there? Can you hear us? Hello
天哪 他们在干什么?
Jesus, what are they doing?
失火了 他们想烧死我们
We're on fire They're trying to burn us out.
哦 天哪
Oh my God
卡莉
Carly
回来 放开我 放手
Come here Let go of me, let go
我宁愿跳下去也不愿被烧死
I'd rather jump than burn to death
冷静点
Calm down
你说的对 什么?
You're right. What?
她说的对 我们必须跳下去 离底下树枝只有几尺高
She's right, we have to jump. the branch is only a few feet down.
似乎超过二十尺呢
It's more like 20 feet.
听着 洁西 我不想这样子被烧死
Look, Jess, I don't want to be burned like this
我不想被砍成肉块 我们行的
I don't want to be chopped into pieces, we can do this.
我先跳
I'll go first
克里斯 嘿
Chris, hey
克里斯 克里斯
Chris, Chris
你没事吧? 你想他们看见我们吗?
You're OK? Do you think this is us?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们得移动 快点 该死 该死
We gotta move. Come on. Shit, shit
卡莉 快点
Carly, come on.
我不行 我不行
I can't do this I can't do this
来吧
Come on.
他来了
He's coming.
我知道 我有个计划 来吧
I know, I have a plan. Come on
洁西 这边
Jessie, this way.
你能抓住这个吗? 为什么?
Can you hold this? Why?
因为我们要将这混蛋弹到树下 你能抓紧吗?
Cause we're gonna knock this fucker out of the tree. Can you hold it?
可以
Yeah
好了 等到我停住不动再放手 好吗?
Alright, don't let go until I cease, OK?
你要去哪里? 我去确保一下他会从这边来
Where are you going? I'm gonna make sure he comes this way.
不 你走路不像我这么快 洁西 洁西
No, you can't walk as quick as I can. Jessie, Jessie
我在这里 来抓我啊
I'm right here. Come and get me.
你们在哪里?
Where are you?
我在这里
Here I am.
你朋友的事很遗憾
Sorry about your friends.
上周五我回家 答录机上有通讯息
Last Friday I came home and there was the message on my machine.
我男友说我们该分手了
From my boyfried who says that we shouldn't be together anymore.
过了二十分钟后 我告诉卡莉
After 20 minutes I've been telling Carly
她叫史考特...
She has Scott and...
...艾凡和法兰西 这个礼拜全体带我出来散散心
...Evan and Francine. All for this week to take me out there
他们就是这种朋友
That was the kind of friends they were.
如今他们死了
And now they're dead.
不是你的错
It's not your fault.
小心
Take care
不 那是你在作梦
No, that are your dreaming.
但愿如此
I wish.
你的腿怎么样? 很痛 可是刚才还不会痛
How's your leg? It hurts, but just got, it didn't hurt...
道路 什么?
Road What?
我们准备下去那里 那就从斜坡下去吧
We're ready to get down there. Get by slope right then
不敢相信
I can't believe it.
我们要怎么下去?
How are you gonna get us down?
你怎么会怀疑呢?
How are you gonna doubt it?
放开我
Let go of me
洁西!
Jessie!
嘿 停车!
Hey, stop!
你疯了吗?
Are you crazy?
快点 我们得赶去 冷静一下
Come on, we gotta move. Just calm down.
你是从失火的塔上通知我来其中一个吗? 我一直到处找你们呢
You're one of them that called me from the fire tower? I've been looking all over for you
拜讬 闭嘴听我说 有人死了 死了 什么人?
Please, shut up and listen. People are dead Dead, what people?
救救我 拜讬
Help me, please.
不
No
放我出去
Let me out here
不
No
救命啊
Help me
你没事了 撑着点 没事了 快点
You're OK, just stay with me. You're alright, come on.
继续努力
Keep working on it
你没事吧? 没事 谢谢
You're OK? Yeah, thank you.
一切都没事了
Everything's alright
克里斯
Chris
放开我
Get off me
开枪打他们
Shoot them.
我只剩一颗子弹
I've got only one shot left.
来吧 你们这些王八蛋
Come on, you motherfuckers.
去死吧!
Just die.